谢谢
Cheers.
科迪
Cody.
该起床了
It's time to get up.
爱的怪物论 翻译：Q
? Well, I saw my baby walking ?
? With another man today ?
? Well I saw my baby walking ?
? When I asked her what's the matter ?
? This is what I heard her say ?
? See you later alligator ?
? After while crocodile ?
准备好了吗 弗莱迪？
You ready, Freddy?
小傻瓜
You're silly.
? See you later alligator ?
? After while crocodile ?
? Can't you see you're in my way now ?
? Don't you know you cramp my style ?
? When I thought of what she told me ?
? Nearly made me lose my head ?
? But the next time that I saw her ?
? Reminded her of what she said ?
? See you later alligator ?
你还好吗 小家伙？
How you doing, buddy?
我们这是在哪？
Where are we?
加利福尼亚
We're in California.
注意看有没有米老鼠
Keep an eye out for Mickey Mouse.
我们可不能撞到他
We don't want to run him over.
? Can't you see you're in my way now ?
? Don't you know you cramp my style ?
? You know my love is just for you ?
? Won't you say that you'll forgive me ?
? And say your love for me is true ?
? I said, wait a minute, 'gator ?
下午好
Good afternoon.
你好啊 小姑娘
Well, hello there, young lady.
那个小家伙跟你在一起吗？
The little one with you?
嗯 在车里睡着了
Yeah, he's buried in there someplace.
车程太长了
It was long drive.
他已经睡熟了
He's fast asleep.
我把钥匙给你 你可以开始搬行李了
Let me give you a key so you can unpack some.
谢谢
Thank you.
要我帮忙吗？
You need any help?
谢谢 不用了
Oh no, thank you.
我们东西不多
I don't have much.
那好
Okay.
有什么需要就告诉我
If you need anything, just let me know.
你有我的电话号码吧？
You've got the number.
有的 兰特里先生 谢谢
I do, Mr. Langtree. Thank you.
这是什么地方？
Oh, what is this place?
是你的新家呀
It's your new home.
啊？
Huh?
是不是很棒？
Isn't it wonderful?
简直像在做梦
It's like a dream.
我们真是太幸运了
How lucky are we?
科迪
Cody.
看看 这是你的房间
Look at your room.
壁纸很有意思吧？
Such fun wallpaper, huh?
还有这张桌子
Oh, and this desk,
太完美了
it's perfect.
你可以在这里写作业
You can do all of your homework right here.
真是太棒了
It's just so great, huh?
外面地方很大
Lots of space out there
你可以和小伙伴们一起玩
to play with all of your new friends.
亲爱的 我再去搬一些行李
All right, honey, I'm going to get some more boxes
然后就做晚饭
in the car and then make dinner.
你还好吗？
Are you okay?
我不太舒服
I don't feel right.
那你先休息一下吧
Well, why don't you lie down for a little bit
睡一会儿
and take a nap.
? Mr. Sandman ?
? Bring me a dream ?
? Make him the cutest ?
? That I've ever seen ?
? Give him two lips ?
? Like roses in clover ?
? Then tell him that his lonesome nights are over ?
? Sandman ?
? I'm so alone ?
? Don't have nobody ?
? To call my own ?
? Please turn on your magic beam ?
? Mr. Sandman, bring me a dream ?
? Tell him that his lonesome nights are over ?
我本来以为我自己在用的
I thought my own
热点洗碗机已经很惊艳了
Hotpoint dishwasher was wonderful,
但是这个新洗碗机才是最棒的
but this new one is the greatest ever.
它采用了全新的无水渍系统
It uses a new system of spotless cleansing,
两遍洗涤剂清洗
two detergent washers,
再加上第二遍漂洗的时候
plus a few drops of this special wetting agent
自动滴入的特殊湿润剂
squirted automatically into the second rinse water.
你知道结果是什么吗？
And do you know what this does?
让水不可能
It makes it impossible
沿着餐具…
for water to collect in drops like...
科迪
Cody.
你能去外面玩儿吗？
Why don't you go play outside, okay?
我要擦地板
I'm about to scrub the floor.
别走远 让我能看见你
Stay near the house where I can see you.
在热点洗碗机中
Sparkling clean
洗得晶莹剔透
when it's washed in a Hotpoint.
请查询号码簿的分类页面
Turn to the classified pages of your phone book.
您能找到最近的热点经销商
That's where you'll find your nearest Hotpoint dealer
商品范围：
for ranges,
冰箱
refrigerators,
自动洗衣机和烘干机
automatic washers and dryers.
科迪
Cody.
科迪？
Cody?
科迪！
Cody!
科迪
Cody.
科迪！
Cody!
你没听到我叫你吗？
Didn't you hear me calling you?
你在这里干什么呢？
What are you doing out here?
跟你说了别走远
I told you to stay near the house.
没干什么
Nothing.
就是...
I was just...
这里有个池塘
it's a pond.
不许在这里玩
I don't you playing near here.
很危险
It's dangerous.
我本来以为我自己在用的 热点洗碗机已经很惊艳了
I thought my own Hotpoint dishwasher was wonderful,
但是这个新洗碗机才是最棒的
but this new one is the greatest ever.
它采用了全新的无水渍系统
It uses a new system of spotless cleansing,
两遍洗涤剂清洗
two detergent washes,
再加上第二遍漂洗的时候
plus a few drops of this special wetting agent,
自动滴入的特殊湿润剂
squirted automatically into the second rinse water.
你知道结果是什么吗？
And you know what this does?
让水不可能
It makes it impossible for water
残留在餐具上 或者沿着餐具滑落
to collect in drops on your dishes.
即使是玻璃餐具和银器
You get spotless dry,
也不会有任何水渍
even on glasses and silver.
在热点洗碗机中
Everything is sparkling clean
一切都会洗得闪闪发光
when it's washed in a Hotpoint.
请查询号码簿的分类页面
Turn to the classified pages of your phone book.
别放手
Don't let go, don't let go.
Don't let go.
别放手
不要害怕
Don't be afraid.
你会没事的
You'll be all right.
最棒的
Greatest ever.
它采用了全新的无水渍系统
It uses a new system of spotless...
妈妈！
Mom, mom!
两遍洗涤剂清洗
Two detergent washes
特殊湿润剂...
plus a few drops of...
妈妈！
Mom!
科迪？
Cody?
怎么了？
What happened?
妈妈 外面...
Mom there's a...
我窗户外面有个怪物
There's a monster outside my window.
亲爱的
No, honey.
你只是做噩梦了
You're just having a bad dream.
不是 你看！
No, look, look, look, look!
好好好
Okay, okay.
我看看
Let's see.
没有 没有怪物
No, no monsters out here.
不过起风暴了
There was a storm out there, though.
可能是这个声音吓到你了吧？
So maybe that's what scared you, huh?
我理解 我也做噩梦了
I know, I was having a bad dream too.
梦里也有怪物吗？
Was there a monster in it?
对 而且非常可怕
Yes, and it was very scary.
但我知道我们两个
But I know that you and I
绝对安全
are completely safe,
就像窝在毯子里的两只小虫子
like two bugs, snug in a rug.
好吗？
Okay?
睡吧 宝贝
Get some rest, babe.
明天还要上学呢
You got school tomorrow.
我不想上学
I don't want to go to school.
但是你必须去
Well, you have to,
这是妈妈说的
Mommy says.
来吧 躺下
Come on, lie down.
躺下
Lay down.
睡吧
Get some sleep.
妈妈
Mom,
能别关门吗？
can you leave the door open?
当然了
Of course.
韦弗医生办公室 请问有什么可以帮您的？
Dr. Weaver's office. How may I help you?
能让韦弗医生接电话吗？
May I speak to Dr. Weaver please?
对不起 女士 这只是他的电话应答服务
I'm sorry, ma'am, this is just his answering service.
您想给他留言吗？
Would you like to leave a message?
不用了 谢谢
No, thank you.
? I don't want to set the world ?
科迪 快点
Cody, hurry up.
第一天上学可不能迟到
You don't want to be late your first day.
? I just want to start ?
? A flame in your heart ?
好了 上学第一天
Okay, first day of school.
有个小窍门
Here's a little tool.
牢记黄金法则
Practice the golden rule
你就能变酷
and you will be Mr. Cool.
我爱你
I love you.
祝你过得愉快
Have a great day, okay?
? No other... ?
? I lost all ambition ?
? For worldly acclaim ?
? I just want to be the one you love ?
? And with your admission ?
? That you feel the same ?
? I'll have reached the goal I'm dreaming of ?
? Believe me ?
? I don't want to set the world on fire ?
? I just want to start ?
? A flame in your heart ?
这是你的办公桌
This is your desk.
放轻松点
Make yourself comfortable.
我去拿些材料 然后就可以开始了
I'll go get some materials and be back and get started.
好的 谢谢
Okay, thank you.
你好
Hi.
我是劳拉
I'm Laura.
简
Jane.
很高兴认识你 简
It's very nice to meet you, Jane.
你这身衣服是从哪来的？
Where'd you get that dress?
这个？
Oh, this?
我...
I...
我是简
This is Jane.
好的 先生 马上
Yes, sir. Right away.
嘿 第一天过得怎么样？
Hey, how was your first day?
还行
It was okay.
有没有交到新朋友？
Did you make any new friends?
没有
No.
肯定很快就能交到的
Well, I'm sure you will in no time.
我们回家
All right, here we go home.
我新工作的第一天很愉快
Well, I had a great first day at work.
那里的女士们都很好
The ladies, they're so nice,
凯西和…呃…
Kathy and, um...
苏珊
Susan.
我跟她们相处得都特别愉快
Well, I just got such a tickle out of all of them.
科迪 快吃呀
Cody, eat your dinner.
我不饿
I'm not hungry.
那就少吃一点
Well, try to eat a little.
巨魔是最大公山羊的两倍大
The troll was twice as big as the biggest Billy goat gruff,
但是公山羊并不害怕
but the Billy goat was not afraid.
他低下头 把角对准巨魔冲了过去
He lowered his horns and ran at the troll,
把他推下桥
pushing him over the bridge.
巨魔愤怒地尖叫着
The troll screamed with fury
他掉进了河里
as he fell into the water
被水流冲走了
and was swept away by the current.
然后 最大的公山羊
Then, the biggest Billy goat gruff
回到草地上跟家人团聚了
joined his family in the meadow
并且告诉他们
and told them they never to worry
以后过桥再也不用担心了
about crossing the bridge again.
结束了
The end.
再读一个故事
Read another one.
不行
Sorry.
时间到了
The time has come
小男孩该数羊睡觉了
for counting sheep for little boys who need their sleep.
躺下吧
Now lie down.
明天还要上学
You've got school tomorrow.
睡觉吧
Got to get some rest.
晚安 可爱的小王子
Goodnight, sweet prince.
别关门 好吗？
Leave the door open, okay?
好的
Okay.
爱你
Love you.
你好 是贝蒂吗？
Hello, Betty?
贝蒂・弗格森？
Betty Ferguson?
是我 你是哪位？
Yes, who's this?
里克・尼尔森
This is Rick Nelson.
哦 大卫的弟弟？
Oh, David's brother?
是的
Yeah.
你想让我周五几点
Say, what time do you want me
来接你去参加舞会？
to pick you up for the dance Friday night?
八点半就很合适
Oh, well, 8:30 would just be wonderful.
嘿 我找到她了
Hey, I found her.
好的 我八点半准时到
Okay, I'll be there at 8:30...
-喂 -劳拉？
- Hello? - Laura?
我本来以为我自己在用的
I thought my own
热点洗碗机已经很惊艳了
Hotpoint dishwasher was wonderful,
但是这个新洗碗机才是最棒的
but this new one is the greatest ever...
它采用了全新的无水渍系统
It uses a new system of spotless cleansing,
两遍洗涤剂清洗
two detergent washes
再加上第二遍漂洗的时候
and a few drops of this special wetting agent
自动滴入的…
squirted automatically.
喂
Hello?
劳拉
Laura.
妈妈
Mother.
妈妈 你怎么能把我的号码告诉斯科特？
Mother, how could you give Scott my number?
科迪
Cody.
劳拉 你去哪儿了？
Laura, where have you been?
他刚给我打了电话
He just called here.
你怎么能这样？
How could you do that?
我没告诉他你的号码
I didn't give him your number.
只告诉了你的几个好朋友
I only gave it to a few of your friends.
为什么？
Why?
你为什么要这样？
Why would you do that?
我跟你说过 不要告诉任何人
I told you not to give it to anyone.
他们是你的朋友啊
They're your friends.
你把我的地址也告诉他了吗？
Did you give him my address too?
他会找上门来吗？
Is he gonna come here?
他不会过去的 劳拉
He's not going to come there, Laura.
他只想和你谈谈
He just wants to talk to you.
他很后悔
He feels so bad.
我不在乎他怎么想
I don't care how he feels.
你知道他做了那种事
I don't know how you can even speak to him
你怎么还能跟他说话？
after what he did.
你应该站在我们这边
You're supposed to be on our side.
外婆就会支持我们
Grandma would be.
我们当然支持你了 劳拉
Of course we're on your side, Laura.
你没有
No you're not.
亲爱的 我去陪你们住几天好吗？
Honey, why don't I come and stay with you for a while?
不用
No. No.
我不需要任何帮助 一切都很好
I don't need any help. Everything's perfect.
妈妈！
Mom!
科迪
Cody.
科迪 怎么了？
Cody, what's wrong?
我的房间里有怪物
There was a monster in my room.
没事的
It's okay. It's okay.
你没事的
You're okay.
妈妈 池塘里的怪物在我房间里！
Mom, the monster from the pond was in my room!
亲爱的 没有怪物
Honey, there's no monster.
你只是做噩梦了
You're just having a bad dream.
你不听我说话
You're not listening to me.
它就在这里
It was right here.
梦很像真的
It doesn't feel like a dream,
我知道 但我保证那只是梦
I know, but it was, I promise.
怪物就在这里
The monster was here.
当我渴望回到你身边时
As I yearn to return to you,
你也会渴望回到我身边
so will you yearn to return to me.
当我们的道路再次交汇
When our paths do cross again,
我们的心也会欣喜地再次交织
our hearts will entwined with ecstasy.
劳拉
Laura,
我还以为你是塞顿夫人的鬼魂呢
I thought you were Mrs. Seton's ghost.
不是 外婆
No, Grandma.
她不喜欢阁楼里
She doesn't like it in the attic.
我只在地下室见过她
I only ever see her in the basement.
我也是
Me too.
你从哪找到这么老的东西？
Where did you find this old thing?
他值得你这么付出吗？
Ugh. Is he really worth the effort?
亲爱的 别哭
Oh, honey, don't cry.
现在的年轻人一定很难吧
I can't even imagine how hard it is to be young these days.
我年轻那时候要简单得多
It was so much simpler back in my time.
真希望能带你一起回到过去
I wish I could take you back there with me.
我也希望
I wish I could too.
你很适合那个时代
You'd fit right in.
谢谢 外婆
Thanks, Grandma.
这是韦弗医生的办公室
This is Dr. Weaver's office.
请问有什么可以帮您？
How may I help you?
是弗朗辛吗？
Hi, Francine?
我是劳拉・巴特勒
It's Laura Butler.
嗨 劳拉
Hi, Laura.
我们一直想联系您
We've been trying to reach you.
韦弗医生刚好进来了 稍等
Oh, Dr. Weaver just walked in, hold on.
劳拉 你好吗？
Laura, how are you?
你好 医生
Hi, Doctor.
我也说不好
I don't know.
怎么回事？
What's going on?
斯科特给我打电话了
Scott called.
你又做梦了吗？
Are you having the dreams again?
是的
Yeah.
我不知道是不是该重新服药
I'm wondering if maybe I should go back on medication.
我更希望不用通过药物来处理
You know, I prefer we didn't handle them through medication.
你能今天过来一趟吗？
Can you come in today?
不行 我不在城里
No, I'm out of town.
你在哪里？
Where are you?
劳拉？
Laura?
我在听
I'm here.
你在哪里？
Where are you?
我可能是想多了
You know, I think I'm just being silly.
一切都会好起来的
Everything will be fine.
-谢谢你 医生 -劳拉？
- Thank you, Doctor. - Laura?
科迪 快点
Cody, hurry up.
我们要迟到了
We're going to be late.
-下午好 -下午好
- Good afternoon. - Good afternoon.
有什么需要帮忙的吗？
What can I do for you?
我只是想跟你说一声
Well, I just wanted to let you know that the,
厨房的水龙头漏水
the kitchen sink was leaking.
所以我把水阀关掉了
So I turned off the water.
可能需要换个新胶圈
Probably just need your new seed washer.
我会去看看的
I'll come by and take a look.
谢谢
Thank you.
而且电视也有问题了
And also the television sort of popped
现在没法看了
and now it's not working.
我们不管电视的事
We're not responsible for the television.
好了 莱诺拉 我会过去看看的
Well, now, Lenora, I'd go by and take a look at it.
但是她得支付零件费用
Well, but she's going to have to pay for the parts
电视是上任租客留下的
and the television was left behind.
不是我们的房子提供的
It's not part of the house.
可以的
That's okay.
你先帮我看看吧
If you wouldn't mind just taking a look.
没问题
Will do.
那好
Okay.
祝你们一天愉快
Well, have a nice day.
你也是 小姑娘
You as well, young lady.
我本来以为我自己在用的
That's how it starts.
热点洗碗机已经很惊艳了
I thought my own Hotpoint dishwasher was wonderful,
但是这个新洗碗机才是最棒的
but this new one is the greatest ever.
它采用了全新的无水渍系统
It uses a new system of spotless cleanser,
两遍洗涤剂清洗
two detergent washes,
再加上第二遍漂洗的时候
plus a few drops of this special wetting agent
自动滴入的特殊湿润剂
squirted automatically in the second rinse water.
你知道结果是什么吗？
And do you know what this does?
让水不可能残留在餐具上
It makes it impossible for water to collect in drops
或者沿着餐具滑落
on your dishes.
即使是玻璃餐具和银器
You get spotless dry,
也不会有任何水渍
even on glasses and silver.
在热点洗碗机中
Everything is sparkling clean
一切都会洗得闪闪发光
when it's washed in a Hotpoint.
科迪
Cody.
请查询号码簿的分类页面
Turn to the classified pages of your phone book.
你能找到距离最近的
That's where you will find
热点经销商
your nearest Hotpoint dealer.
冰箱
Refrigerators,
自动洗衣机和...
automatic washers and...
科迪！
Cody!
我想回家
I want to go home.
安泊尔
Amber.
这是你做的？
Is this you?
是你做的？
You did this?
你确定吗？
Are you sure?
我在想是不是你来我家处理事情
So I thought maybe you had come by the house for something.
没有 可能是浣熊吧
No, no, probably a raccoon.
它们哪里都能钻进去
They climb all over the place.
太讨厌了
Bunch of pests.
我觉得不是浣熊
No, I don't think this was a raccoon.
我儿子说他在池塘边看到了一些东西
My son said that he saw something down by the pond.
他不该去池塘那里
He's not supposed to be at the pond.
我不想让他去那里玩
I don't want him playing near there.
我知道 我已经…
Yes, I know. I have, uh,
我已经告诉他不要过去了
I've already told him to stay away from it.
我可以设一些捉浣熊的陷阱
I can set some traps from the raccoons.
我真的认为不是浣熊
Again, I really don't think it was a raccoon.
所以陷阱应该没用
So I don't think that that would be helpful.
我昨晚出去查看的时候
Oh, but I did manage to lock myself out
把自己锁在了房子外面…
of the house last night when I went to investigate and...
等等 这不可能
Wait, that's impossible.
门不会自己锁住...
The door doesn't lock on its own...
那就是卡住了
Well, then I guess it was stuck.
-你必须... -总之呢
- Well you need... - Anyway.
我只好打破门上的窗户爬进去
I had to break the window on the door to get in.
所以我很抱歉
So I'm so sorry.
我们已经修好了水龙头
We already fixed the sink.
不会再付钱修窗户了
We're not paying for that window.
是你弄坏的
You broke it.
我当然会支付窗户的费用了
Of course I will pay for the window.
你有空的时候可以随时过来
Anytime you can stop by.
不用担心
Don't you worry.
我来处理
I'll take care of it.
谢谢
Thank you.
嘿 今天过得怎么样？
Hey, how was your day?
你不会还在生我的气吧？
You're not still mad at me, are you?
亲爱的 我跟你道歉了
Honey, I said I was sorry.
要不要吃冰淇淋？
How about some ice cream?
嗯？
Huh?
好
Yeah.
科迪 你为什么不去玩？
Cody, why don't you go play?
很有趣啊
This looks fun.
踢球
Kickball.
你为什么不去和他们一起玩？
Why don't you go play with them?
他们是朋友
They're friends.
那个小朋有在自己玩
Well, this kid's all by himself.
他看起来需要一个朋友
He looks like he could use a friend.
你去跟他一起玩吧？
Why don't you go ask him to play?
他是个笨蛋
He's a dipstick.
也许你可以帮他成为一个更好的人
Well, maybe you could help him be a better person.
对吧？
Right?
去吧 跟他一起玩
Go on. Go ask him to play.
我帮你拿着冰淇淋
I'll hold your ice cream.
我不想
I don't want to.
去 邀请他一起玩
Go on, ask him to play.
我们走吧
Let's go.
怎么了？他不想玩？
What happened? He didn't want to play?
对 我早说了 走吧
No, I told you, let's go.
科迪 他对你说了什么吗？
Cody, did he say something to you?
没有 别再说了行不行？
No, God, forget it, okay?
科迪
Cody.
科迪 我知道你在这里不开心
Cody, I know you're not happy here.
我们不会回梅萨的 你知道原因
We are not going back to Mesa and you know why.
因为你讨厌爸爸
Because you hate Dad.
我不是讨厌爸爸
No, I don't hate Dad.
我是讨厌爸爸对我们做的事
I hate what Dad did to us.
所以我必须确保
And I'm going to make very sure
他不会再伤害我们了
that he can never hurt us again.
我已经原谅他了
Well, I forgive him.
你这样想我很骄傲
I'm so proud of you for that.
但我还没准备好
But I'm not ready.
也许有一天我也会原谅他
Maybe someday.
但在那之前
In the meantime,
我们能试着在这里开心地生活吗？
can we try to be happy living here?
拜托了
Please?
你在画什么？
What you drawing?
漂亮的女士
The pretty lady.
什么漂亮的女士？
What pretty lady?
池塘里的那个
From the pond.
你不是说池塘里的是个怪物吗？
I thought you said it was a monster in the pond.
我本来以为是怪物
I thought there was a monster in the pond,
但是她到我的房间跟我说话
but then she came to my room and talked to me.
现在我明白了
Now I understand.
明白什么？
Understand what?
来见见她吧 妈妈
Come meet her, Mom.
跟她聊聊
Come talk to her.
我们去池塘吧
Let's go to the pond.
我不想去池塘
I don't wanna go to the pond.
好吧 那只能等她来找你了
Well, then I guess she'll just have to come to you.
你知道我想要什么吗？
You know what I would love?
我非常希望
I would love it
你给我画一张你学校的画
if you would draw me a picture of your school or,
或者画一只鸟
or what about a bird?
我们可以把你的画贴在冰箱上
And we can put your drawings up on the fridge.
会很漂亮的
It'll look so nice.
你看到漂亮女士了吗？
Did you see the pretty lady?
妈妈 她跟你说话了吗？
Did she talk to you, Mom?
科迪 睡吧
Cody, go to sleep.
妈妈 我爱你
I love you, Mom.
科迪
Cody.
我说午饭做好了
I said lunch was ready.
好的
Okay.
够了
That's enough.
还给我！
Give it back!
科迪・理查德・巴特勒
Cody Richard Butler.
不许你再这么做了！
Don't you ever do that again.
科迪
Cody.
你为什么这么生我的气？
Why are you so angry at me?
我不能告诉你
I can't tell you.
是因为你的生日吗？
Is it about your birthday?
我没忘
I didn't forget.
我的生日？
My birthday?
我正要问你想怎么庆祝呢
I was going to ask you what you wanted to do.
除了这个 什么都行
Anything but that.
嘿 我在想
Hey, I was thinking,
开个派对怎么样？
how about we have a party?
我们可以…
We can,
买好多气球
we can have balloons
还有冰淇淋、蛋糕和礼物
and ice cream and cake and presents,
可以把你全班同学都请来
and we can invite your entire class.
肯定很好玩 对吧？
It'll be a gas, right?
好吧
Okay.
好
不过我不介意 这让他开心
I don't mind, though. Keeps him happy.
我相信我们的热点冰箱也不介意....
I'm sure our Hotpoint refrigerator doesn't mind either...
嘿 他长得跟罗伊・罗杰斯很像
Hey, he looks just like Roy Rogers.
你喜欢罗伊・罗杰斯 对吧？
You like Roy Rogers, right?
我觉得在戴夫和瑞奇成家立业之后
I have a feeling it'll be with us
它还会陪伴我们很久
long after Dave and Ricky are grown up and married.
我也喜欢热点的设计
And I love the way our Hotpoint's designed too.
本来可以...
It could've been...
所有的内部设计都非常实用
All the interior arrangements are so practical.
今天就给热点经销商谈谈
Why don't you talk to your Hotpoint dealer today
给你家也添置一台这样的冰箱吧
about a refrigerator like this for your family?
请查询号码簿的分类页面
Turn to the classified pages of your phone book.
可以找到离你家最近的热点经销商
That's where you will find your nearest Hotpoint dealer.
好了
There.
邀请函都准备好了
Now there are exactly enough invitations
足够发给你们班的所有同学
for every kid in your class.
一定要给每人都发一张 好吗？
So I want you to make sure that everyone gets one, okay?
他们不会来的
They won't come.
当然会来啊
Of course they will.
所有人都喜欢派对
Everyone loves a party.
-我能邀请漂亮女士吗？ -谁？
- Can I invite the pretty lady? - Who?
池塘里的漂亮女士
The pretty lady from the pond.
不行
No. No, you can't.
为什么？ 她是我最好的朋友
Why not? She's my best friend.
她说她会带我回家
She said that she would take me home.
科迪
Cody.
这里就是你的家
This is your home.
知道吗？
Okay?
你就跟她谈谈吧 妈妈
If you would just talk to her, Mom.
科迪 够了
Cody, that's enough.
把玩具收好 该上床睡觉了
Clean up your toys. It's almost bedtime.
当她来的时候 她会绕山而来
? She'll be coming around the mountain when she comes ?
她会绕山而来
? She'll be coming around the mountain ?
? She'll be coming around in the mountain ?
当她来的时候 她会绕山而来
? She'll be coming around the mountain when she comes ?
她来了
Here she comes.
科迪
Cody.
上楼 躲进衣柜里
Go upstairs, hide in your closet.
别出声
Do not make a sound.
不 没事的 妈妈
No, it's okay, Mom. It's okay.
-听我说 不用害怕！ -科迪 快走
- Listen to me. Don't be afraid! - Cody, just go.
科迪 你还好吧？
Cody, are you okay?
妈妈
Mom. Mom.
Mom, Mom.
你摔倒了
You fell down.
快走
Come on. Come on.
-妈妈 你在干什么？ -上车
- Mom, what are you doing? - Get in the car.
-为什么？ -快上车
- Why? - Just get in.
-但是 妈妈... -上车！
- But, Mom... - Get in the car!
-我们要去哪？ -只要离开这里 去哪都行
- Where are we going? - Anywhere but here.
为什么？她吓到你了？
But why? Because she scared you?
她不是故意吓唬你的 妈妈
She didn't mean to scare you, Mom.
科迪 闭嘴！
Be quiet, Cody!
你得跟她谈谈 妈妈
You need to talk to her, Mom.
她不会伤害你的 她不会伤害任何人！
She would never hurt you. She wouldn't hurt anyone!
够了 科迪！
Enough, Cody! Enough!
我不知道那是什么东西
I don't not know what that thing is
但是你永远不许再跟它说话了！
but you are never talking to it again.
明白吗？永远！
Do you understand? Ever!
你要带我回家吗？
Are you gonna take me home?
不 该死的 我说了无数遍了
No, goddammit, for the hundredth time.
我们不回家
We're not going home.
别再提这事了
Stop talking about that.
那我们要去哪？
Then where are we going?
我该怎么办？
What am I supposed to do?
没事的 妈妈
It's okay, Mom.
她走了
She's gone.
我会让她不要再去找你了
I'll tell her not to bother you anymore.
好吗？
Okay?
你该睡觉了 你累了
You should go to bed. You're tired.
我会陪着你的 好吗？
I'll stay with you, okay?
我们会没事的
We'll be all right.
我保证
I promise.
我们会没事的
We're gonna be all right.
你准备好了？
You ready?
我希望你一到学校
Now, I want you to give these out
就把这些都发出去 好吗？
as soon as you get to school, okay?
-好的 -很好
- Okay. - Okay.
就放在这里
Put 'em right in here.
你好 接线员
Hello, operator,
请帮我转接圣玛丽教堂吗？
will you connect me with St. Mary's church please?
谢谢
Thank you.
圣玛丽教堂
Saint Mary's.
艾格尼丝修女
Sister Agnes speaking.
你好
Hi.
不知道有没有人
I was wondering if there might be someone available
能跟我谈谈？
to speak with me?
我 我想...
I, I think...
我觉得我家里有恶魔之类的东西
I think I have a demon or something in my house.
喂？
Hello?
朗特里先生有空吗？
Is Mr. Langtree available?
怎么了 你又把什么东西弄坏了？
Why, what'd you break this time?
没有
Oh. Nothing, nothing.
我就是 呃…
I just, um...
我不知道该怎么说
I don't, I don't know exactly how to say this.
直说就行了
Well, just say it.
有没有人说过
Has anyone ever said
那座房子有什么不对劲？
that there's something wrong with the house?
你到底想干什么 小姐？
What are you up to, missy?
什么意思？
What do you mean?
因为你搬进那所房子之前
Because you knew exactly what you were getting into
就已经知道房子的状况了
when you moved into the house.
如果你觉得你可以穿着那条小裙子
So if you think that you can come sashaying in here
在这里搞点小动作
in that little skirt
就可以骗我们在那房子上投入一大笔钱
and con us into putting a whole bunch of money into that place,
我丈夫可能会蠢到上你的当
my husband might be stupid enough to fall for that,
但我不会
but I'm not.
我没想让你们干什么事
I'm not trying to do anything.
那我不明白你来这里干什么
Well, I don't know what you're doing here
除非你在隐瞒什么
in the first place, unless you're hiding something.
我是想问...
I am trying to ask you...
那栋房子里是不是有鬼
if there's a ghost in the house.
鬼？
A ghost!
你吸毒了吗？
Is it drugs?
没有
No, no.
我可是有孩子的人
I have a child.
如果再让我听到
Because if I get wind
那座房子里闹鬼之类的屁话
that any of that crap is going on in that house,
我就要报警了
I'm going to call the police,
到时候警察肯定会把你的孩子带走
and you can be sure of the fact they'll take your child away from you.
? Every day ?
? It's a gettin' closer ?
吹这么多气球干什么？
What are we going to do with all these balloons?
挂起来
Oh, we're going to hang them.
从这里开始
I'm going to hang from here,
沿着这里挂一排
and then along there.
也许那里也挂几个
And maybe over there.
肯定很好看
It's gonna look great.
所有人都会喜欢的
Everyone's gonna love it.
? Hey, hey, hey ?
? Everyday, it's a getting faster ?
? Everyone ?
听起来像放屁
It sounds like I farted.
你也试试 妈妈
You do it, Mom.
? Love like yours ?
? Will surely come my way ?
? Hey, hey, hey ?
是谁在切奶酪？
Who cut the cheese?
? Everyday seems a little longer ?
? Every way, love's a little stronger ?
? Come what may ?
? Do you ever long for ?
? True love from me ?
? Everyday, it's a gettin' closer ?
? Goin' faster than a roller coaster ?
? Love like yours will surely come my way ?
? Hey, hey, hey ?
完美
Perfect.
别担心 他们肯定会来的
Don't worry, I'm sure they're coming.
可能有些人迷路了
You know, I bet some of them even got lost.
大家参加派对的时候总是迟到
And people love to come late to parties.
你到时候就知道了
You'll see.
也许我应该打几个电话问问
Maybe I should give a few of them a call.
厨房里好像有一份学校的联系表
I think I have a class list from the school in the kitchen.
马上回来
Be right back.
他们应该不会来了 小家伙
I don't think they're coming, buddy.
我知道
I know.
别觉得这是针对你的 好吗？
I don't want you to take it personally, okay?
我们住得离市区太远了
We live really far out of town.
有些人只是…
You know, some people, they just,
没那么多时间来这么远的地方
they can't spend the time driving out here.
好吗？
Okay?
明年我们找家茶餐厅给你办派对
But hey, next year we'll have your party
或者披萨店
at the malt shop or the pizza parlor.
肯定很有意思
That'll be fun.
好的
Okay.
要打开你的礼物吗？
Do you wanna open your presents?
暂时不要了
Not right now.
我现在只想上楼回房间
I think I'm just going to go upstairs.
你确定吗？
You sure?
好的
Okay.
别往这里打电话了 斯科特
Stop calling here, Scott.
求你别挂我的电话 劳拉
Please don't hang up on me, Laura.
求你跟我谈谈吧
Please talk to me.
该说的我都已经说过了
I've said everything I ever want to say to you.
对不起 我真的很抱歉
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
我想你 想我儿子
I miss you. I miss my son.
那你最好习惯这一点
Well, you better get used to it
因为你再也见不到我们了
because you'll never see either one of us ever again.
我也喜欢热点的设计
And I love the way our Hotpoint's designed too.
简直是为我量身定做的
It could have been made for me.
内部设计都非常实用
The interior arrangements are all so practical.
科迪！
Cody!
为什么？
Why?
你为什么没送出去？
Why didn't you hand these out?
我花了那么多时间
I spent all that time
想把你的生日派对办好
making a special day for your birthday
而你就坐在那里
and you just sat there.
坐在那里看我忙来忙去
You just sat there and watched me do it.
但你根本连邀请信都没送出去！
And you didn't even hand out the invitations!
为什么？
Why?
为什么要这样？
Why would you do that?
科迪
Cody.
科迪 不
Cody, no.
科迪 回来
Cody, come back here.
科迪
Cody,
科迪 停下
Cody, stop it right now.
-告诉我！ -因为他们不会来的
- Now, tell me! - Because they wouldn't come.
你不听我说话 你不听任何人说话！
You don't listen to me. You don't listen to anyone!
你怎么知道？
How would you know that?
你根本没给他们机会
You didn't even give them a chance.
因为我跟他们不一样
Because I'm not like them.
我讨厌这里
I hate it here.
我想回家
I want to go home.
我们不会回去的 明白了吗？
We are not going back there. Do you hear me?
科迪
Cody.
科迪 怎么…
Cody, what...
你怎么了？
What is wrong with you?
科迪
Cody, Cody,
别这样
please.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
好了
Okay.
跟妈妈一起呼吸 深呼吸
Breathe with Mommy. Breathe, baby.
如果你又感觉不舒服了
If you start to feel bad again,
就告诉老师 好吗？
you just tell the teacher, okay?
好
Okay.
劳拉
Laura.
劳拉！
Laura!
一个小时之内 把新的DM40放在我的桌子上
I need that new DM 40 on my desk in an hour.
DM40是文件中最重要的表格
The DM4's the most crucial form in the file.
嘿 科迪 今天过得怎么样？
Hey, Cody, how was your day?
-还可以 -是吗？
- It was okay. - Yeah?
科迪 你是不是捉弄那些小姑娘了？
Cody, have you been teasing those little girls?
没有
No.
你确定吗？
Are you sure?
嗯
Yes.
她们好像在跟老师告你的状
'Cause I can see them tattling on you to a teacher.
在我今晚接到老师电话之前
Do you want to give me your side of the story
你想给我讲讲你那版本的故事吗？
before I get a call tonight?
我什么也没做
I didn't do anything.
好吧 那我就等电话吧
All right, I'll wait for the call.
兰特里夫人？
Mrs. Langtree?
哦 你好
Oh, oh, hello.
我只是在检查设备
I was just checking on the appliances.
-真的吗？ -是的
- Really? - Yeah.
我不这么认为 你是在窥探吧
I don't think so. I think you were snooping.
找到你想找的毒品了吗？
Did you find the drugs you were looking for?
这是我的房子
You know, this is my house
所以我可以随时来检查
so I can actually check on it anytime I want.
没有我的许可你就不可以
Not without my permission, you can't.
如果你想确定这一点
And if you'd like to validate that,
我们可以让警察跟你说
we can call the police.
警察？
The police?
是的
Mm-hmm.
你是有什么毛病吗？
Is there something wrong with you?
因为我觉得这座房子里有些事情
Because I think there's something terribly wrong
非常不对劲
going on in this house.
如果你搞清楚了
Well, when you figure it out,
能告诉我一声吗？
will you give me a holler?
因为我太想知道了
Because I would just love to know.
我要求你从这里搬走
I want you out of this house.
你有30天
You have 30 days.
给我书面通知
Put it in writing.
我会的
Oh, I will.
30天
30 days.
? Doo wop a doo wop, shoopi doobi doo wop ?
? She give me Katchi ?
? All night long ?
? Well, well, well ?
? It's been a long day ?
? I'm kinda tired, bring your soothing arms my way ?
? My back is achin' and my body sore ?
? Don't stop, honey, you know that I want more ?
? She give me Katchi ?
? All night long ?
? All night ?
当她来的时候 她会绕山而来
? She'll be coming around the mountain when she comes ?
她会绕山而来
? She'll be coming around the mountain ?
当她来的时候 她会绕山而来
? She'll be coming around the mountain when she comes ?
科迪 不！
Cody, no!
科迪
Cody.
你好
Hello.
你在哪？
Where are you?
我已经准备好了
I'm ready.
科迪？
Cody?
科迪 停下！
Cody, stop!
科迪
Cody, Cody.
呼吸
Please breathe.
呼吸 宝贝
Breathe, baby.
对 就这样 宝贝
There. That's right, baby. That's right.
你没事了
You're okay.
哦 科迪
Oh, Cody. Cody.
科迪
Cody.
我收到过很多次投诉
I've had repeated complaints
关于DM40归档不正确或者不完整
about the DM 40 being filed incorrectly or incomplete,
没有给文件附上正确的信函
not attaching your correspondence to the proper files.
我会努力改进的
I'll try to get better at that.
为审计员妥善维护档案
It's extremely important that you maintain
是非常重要的
proper maintenance of the files for the auditors.
准确性是对我们的评分标准
We're graded on accuracy.
如果达不到某个标准 我们是要交罚款的
There're fines implemented if we don't meet a certain standard.
我明白
I understand.
劳拉 我要问你一个私人问题
Laura, I have to ask you a personal question.
你是不是一直在喝酒？
Have you been drinking?
我知道你喝了 我能闻到
I know you have. I can smell it.
我们不能容忍在工作时间饮酒
We don't tolerate drinking on the job.
这在员工手册中已经明确写出了
That's clearly stated in your employee handbook.
是的
Yes, it is.
我知道 因为我读过
I know because I read it.
但如果让你过我的生活 你也会喝酒的
But I think that if you had my job, you'd be drinking too.
离开你的家人和朋友
You try leaving your family and your friends
以及你熟悉的一切
and everything you've ever known
搬到一个偏僻的小镇
to move to this small town in the middle of nowhere,
只能靠自己
all by yourself,
因为没有人给你任何其他选择 先试试这些
simply because no one gave you any other choice.
然后再跟我谈工作期间饮酒的事
Then talk to me about drinking on the job.
劳拉 听着
Laura, look.
或者我们有一份
Or maybe there's a company manual
关于如何摆脱怪物的员工手册
on how to get rid of a monster.
而且我不是在谈论我的前夫
And I'm not talking about my ex-husband
也不是在说让我喘不过来气的压力
or my entire overwhelming situation.
我是在说一个真正的怪物
No, I am talking about an actual monster
它半夜来到我家
who comes into my house in the middle of the night
想把我儿子拖出去
and tries to drag my son out
淹死在房子后面的池塘里
and drown him in a pond out back.
我知道你觉得我疯了
I know you think I'm nuts.
不
No.
我没这么想
I don't think that.
我觉得你需要帮助
I think you need help.
我不需要帮助
I do not need help.
一切都在我的控制中
I have everything completely under control.
才不是呢
No, you don't.
我们完全可以帮助你这样的女性
There's no reason we can't help women like you.
上面有电话号码
There's a number there.
打电话 跟护士或者咨询师谈谈
Call it, speak to a nurse or counselor.
我觉得这个应该留给你
Actually, I think you should keep this
因为我不需要你的帮助
because I don't want your help
也不需要你可怜的工作
and I don't want your miserable job.
那就走吧
Then go.
我走了 老爹
I'm gone, daddy-o.
? Doo wop a doo wop, shoopi doobi doo wop ?
? She give me Katchi ?
? All night long ?
? Well, well, well ?
? It's been a long day ?
? I'm kinda tired, bring your soothing arms my way ?
哇
Whoa.
看着你
Look at you.
琴吉・罗杰斯 （注：美国著名演员）
Ginger Rogers.
你的啤酒喝完了
Your beer is empty.
我再给你买一瓶
I'm going to buy you another.
酒保 再给他来一瓶
Bartender, can he have another?
我要一瓶这个
And can I have another one of those?
别这样
No, no, no, please.
我不能让你请我喝酒
You, you don't buy me a drink.
别这样 我在庆祝
Come on, I'm celebrating.
庆祝什么？
Oh, what are we celebrating?
我今天辞职了
I quit my job today.
我讨厌它 所以就辞了
I hated it so I quit it.
好姑娘
Atta girl.
我喜欢你的风格
I like your style.
这样吧 如果你跟我跳支舞
I'll tell you what, I'll get you that drink
我就请你喝酒
if you come dance with me.
哦
Oh.
来吧
Come on.
就一支舞
One dance.
你知道这首歌吗？
You know this song?
不知道
Mm-mm.
很老了 慢慢被人遗忘了
Yeah, well, it's old and forgotten.
有点像我
Kinda like me.
但是你
But, you,
年轻又漂亮
you are a pretty young thing
穿着漂亮的小圆点连衣裙
in a pretty little polka dot dress.
看起来像个天使
You look like an angel.
我的意思是...
I mean like...
就好像我已经死了 现在身处天堂
like I died and went to heaven.
我确实当过天使
I was an angel once
在教堂的一次戏剧演出里
in a play at church.
我外婆给我做了漂亮的天使翅膀
My grandmother made me the most beautiful angel wings.
我觉得穿上那些翅膀好像就能飞了
I felt like I could fly in those wings.
像你这样的女孩
A girl like you,
不需要翅膀就能飞翔
you don't need wings to fly.
对 我有车
No, I have a car.
对 这就行了
Oh, well, that'll do.
车确实很有用
That's pretty good.
那你接下来要做什么 天使？
So what are you going to do next, angel?
我不知道
I don't know.
嘿
Hey, hey, hey.
别哭呀
Don't cry.
别哭
你会想出办法的
You're going to figure something out.
我想去别的地方
I just wish I could go somewhere else,
一个新的地方
you know, somewhere new
然后重新开始
and start fresh.
就是…重新开始
Just, just start over.
那你就走吧
Then you go,
找出你漂亮的小翅膀
you dig out those pretty little wings of yours
然后展翅高飞
and you fly, fly, fly.
科迪
Cody.
你认识科迪・巴特勒吗？
Do you know Cody Butler?
你见过科迪・巴特勒吗？
Have you seen Cody Butler?
没有？
No.
科迪？
Cody?
你认识科迪・巴特勒吗？
Do you know Cody Butler?
嘿 你认识科迪・巴特勒吗？
Hey, do you know Cody Butler?
科迪？
Cody?
嘿 你认识科迪・巴特勒吗？
Hey, hey, do you know Cody Butler?
不认识？
No?
你见过科迪・巴特勒吗？
Have you seen Cody Butler?
你好吗 女士？
How are you today, ma'am?
警官 我来接我儿子
Officer, I came to pick up my son
但是我到处都找不到他
and I can't find him anywhere.
没事的 女士
Okay, okay. It's all right, ma'am.
你儿子叫什么名字？
What's your son's name?
他叫科迪・巴特勒
His name is Cody Butler.
他是二年级的学生
He's a second grade student.
我怕是我的前夫
I'm afraid that my ex-husband
没告诉我就把他接走了
has taken him without my knowledge.
-没事 我们会查清楚的 好吗？ -好的
Okay, well, we're going to get to the bottom of this, okay? - Okay.
你有什么身份证件吗？
Do you, do you have any identification?
科迪的？
For Cody?
不是 女士 你的证件
No, ma'am, your identification.
嗨 劳拉
Hi, Laura.
我是巴布・希夫
I'm Barb Schiff.
我是局里的社工
I'm a caseworker with the department.
抱歉让你等了这么久
I'm sorry it took me so long to get here.
你还好吗？
How are you?
科迪在哪？
Where is Cody?
我去学校接他 他不在
I went to school to pick him up and he was not there.
对 他不在
No, he wasn't.
你觉得他在哪里？
Where do you think he is?
他爸爸把他接走了？
Does his dad have him?
不是 他没有
No, he doesn't.
你怎么知道？
How do you know?
你给他打电话了？
Did you call him?
我不用打电话
I didn't need to.
你什么意思？
What do you mean?
劳拉
Laura,
我们能不能先同步下信息？
would you mind if we backed up a little bit?
如果我能了解科迪事故的细节
I think I could be of more help
我应该能给你提供更多帮助
if I understood the details of Cody's accident.
我指的是去年在亚利桑那发生的事故
I'm referring to the accident last year in Arizona.
哦
Oh.
不是大事
Well, that was nothing.
他掉进了游泳池
He fell in the pool.
我当时不在
I wasn't there.
我去超市买东西了
I had to go to the grocery store.
他父亲在家看着他
His father was watching him.
我到家的时候 斯科特正坐在沙发上看球赛
When I came home, Scott was on the couch, watching the game
我走进厨房
and I went into the kitchen
有一种奇怪的感觉 好像出了什么事
and I had this weird feeling like something wrong.
而我站在水池边
And I was standing at the sink
看着窗外的游泳池
and I was looking out the window at the pool
好像看到里面有什么东西
and I thought I saw something in it.
我出去检查 发现是他
When I went out to check, I saw that it was him.
然后发生了什么？
And then what happened?
我把他拖了出来
Well, I dragged him out
给他做了心肺复苏术
and I performed CPR on him
然后急救人员到了
until the paramedics came
他活过来了 完全没事了
and then they revived him and he was completely okay.
为什么问这个？
Why?
你的意思是发生了这件事
Are you saying there's something wrong with him
让他有后遗症了？
because of what happened?
不 我不是这个意思
No, that is not what I'm saying.
没事的 劳拉
It's okay, Laura.
你没事的
You're all right.
我要喝点水
I think I need some water.
好的
Okay.
你在这里坐着
You sit tight.
我去给你倒水
I'll get you one.
她会绕山而来
? She'll be coming around the mountain ?
科迪！
Cody!
当她来的时候 她会绕山而来
? She'll be coming around the mountain when she comes ?
她会绕山而来
? She'll be coming around the mountain ?
科迪！
Cody!
她会绕山而来
? She'll be coming around the mountain ?
当她来的时候 她会绕山而来
? She'll be coming around the mountain when she comes ?
科迪 开门
Cody, open the door.
-科迪 你在哪？  -我就在这里
- Cody, where are you? - I'm right here.
科迪！
Cody! Cody.
怎么回事？
What happened?
你去哪儿了？
Where have you been?
亲爱的 你为什么不等我去学校接你？
Honey, why didn't you wait for me to pick you up from school?
我该回家了 妈妈
It's time for me to go home, Mom.
不不不
No, no, no.
我带你去别的地方 好吗？
I'm going to take you somewhere else, okay?
我带你离开这里
I'm going to take you away from here.
你就是想离开这里 对吧？
That's what you want, right?
我们去收拾行李装车
We're going to pack up the car
去一个全新的地方
and we're going to go somewhere brand new
有一个全新的开始 好吗？
and we're going to have a fresh start, okay?
好吗？
Okay?
我不想
I don't want to.
你必须去 这是妈妈说的
Well, you have to. Mommy says.
上楼收拾东西
So go upstairs and pack up your stuff.
科迪 你要去哪？
Cody, where are you going?
-我不要跟你走 -不
- I'm not going. - No. No.
-求你了 -不！
- Please. - No!
求你了！
Please, let me...!
-科迪 上楼 -放我离开吧！
- Cody, go upstairs. - Please, let me go!
-科迪！  -求你了！
- Cody! - Please!
不！科迪！停下！
No! Cody! Stop it! Stop it!
对不起
I'm so sorry.
科迪
Cody, Cody, Cody.
Cody.
科迪
科迪 求你了 别离开我
Cody, please don't leave me.
我想和漂亮的女士一起走
I want to go with the pretty lady.
不行
No, no.
别这么说
Don't say that.
你想和我在一起
You want to stay here with me.
你必须让我离开 妈妈
You have to let me go, Mom.
为什么？
Why?
那不是你的错 妈妈
It wasn't your fault, Mom.
那不是谁故意的
It wasn't on purpose.
是一个意外
It was an accident.
没事的
It's okay.
怎么会没事
It's not okay.
会没事的 你会看到的
It will be, you'll see.
求你了 科迪 我不想让你离开我
Please, Cody, I don't want you to leave me.
你必须让我走 妈妈
You have to let me go, Mom.
求你了
Please. Please.
真不敢相信她居然会这么做
I can't believe she did this.
这是管道爆裂
The pipe burst.
是她弄坏的 吉姆
She broke it, Jim.
那是什么？
What's that?
吉姆
Jim, Jim.
吉姆 那张纸是什么？
Jim, what's that piece of paper?
递给我就行...
Just hand me...
（外婆的新车 1959年）
? Just you know why ?
? Why you and I ?
? Will bye and bye ?
? Know true love ways ?
? Sometimes we'll sigh ?
应该可以了 你可以上路了
All right, that should do it. You're good to go.
太好了 谢谢你
Great. Thank you.
-你说要去哪来着？ -回家 梅萨
- Where did you say you were headed again? - Home. Mesa.
你的车应该能撑到那里
Oh, it'll make it there.
? With those who really care ?
? Sometimes we'll sigh ?
? Sometimes we'll cry ?
? And we'll know why ?
? Just you and I ?
? Know true love ways ?
? Throughout the days ?
? Our true love ways ?
? Will bring us joys to share ?
? With those who really care ?
? Sometimes we'll sigh ?
? Sometimes we'll cry ?
? And we'll know why ?
? Just you and I ?
? Know true love ways ?